cashtasks.com 2018-06-20

# About: Privacy Policy - ClixSense

Last Updated May 24, 2018

**What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site, fill out a form or engage in any other activity on or use of our site. When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, date of birth or gender. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. We believe in minimizing data collected and limiting its use and purpose to only that 1) for which we have been given permission by customers, 2) as necessary to deliver our services and 3) as we might be required or permitted for legal, compliance or other lawful purposes.

We also collect information about aggregate site usage. We may automatically collect certain usage information from users, such as Internet Protocol ("IP") addresses, unique device identifiers, pages viewed, browser type, any links you click on to leave or interact with our services and other usage information collected from cookies and other tracking technologies as noted below. For example, we collect IP addresses to track and aggregate non-personal information, such as using IP addresses to monitor the regions from which users navigate to our Services. We also collect IP addresses from users when they log into their accounts as part of our log-in process and for enhanced identity authentication and authorization security.

**What do we use your information for?**  
The main reason we collect information from our users is to help identify potentially suitable participants for surveys we administer for third parties, or to conduct those surveys. In addition, any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To personalize your experience - Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs; 
  * To improve our website - We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you; 
  * To improve customer service - Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs; 
  * To process transactions - Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested; 
  * To administer a contest, promotion or other site features; 
  * To send periodic emails - The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

**How do we protect your information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information we collect, depending on the nature of the information and the context. These measures include administrative (e.g., internal security policies), technical (e.g., encryption) and physical (e.g., secure data centers) controls.

**International Transfers**  
If you are visiting our site from outside the United States, be aware that your information will be transferred to, and maintained on, computers located within the United States. The collection, use, retention and any other processing of your information will be governed by United States law, although we comply with the European Union ("EU") General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) to the extent applicable regarding users who are residents of EU member states.

**What information do we collect from children?**  
We do not intentionally collect any information from children under 16 years of age. However, if a child under 16 years of age navigates to our website, we may store session data on their browser as we would with any other visitor. If you have reason to believe that a child under 16 years of age has provided us with personal information, please contact us by clicking the 'Contact Us' link found at the bottom of our site.

**Do we use cookies?**  
We use Cookies (small files placed on your hard drive through your Web browser - if you allow - that enables us to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information). A few important things you should know about cookies are that: 

  * We offer certain features that are available only through the use of cookies; 
  * We use cookies to help identify you and maintain your signed-in status; 
  * Most cookies are 'session cookies', meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session; 
  * You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although doing so may interfere with your use of some of our sites or services; 
  * You may encounter cookies from third parties on certain pages of the sites that we do not control. (For example, if you view a web page created by another user, there may be a cookie placed by that web page.)

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information without your consent. We may share such information with trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or other’s rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

For EU residents, we treat GDPR Personal Data you provide in accordance with the GDPR. We may share certain Personal Data with trusted third parties for whom we administer surveys or other services, or who provide services to us, where you provide consent and where such third parties have agreed to the EU standard contractual clauses for data protection addenda or have otherwise indicated that they are eligible for such sharing or comply with the GDPR.

ClixSense may share your personal information and/or social-demographic information, including, without limitation, a unique identification number ("UID"), postal code, gender, marital status, education, ethnicity/race (where permitted by applicable law), employment related information, and non-personally identifiable information on household members, with third party sample/market research companies (individually each a “Third Party MR Company” and collectively the “Third Party MR Companies”) for the following purposes:

  1. Identifying client survey opportunities that you may be eligible for, through the Third-Party MR Companies; and 
  2. Disclosing such data elements to clients of the Third-Party MR Companies for audience measurement services; and 
  3. Appending such data elements to completed client surveys and delivering the appended survey data to clients of the Third-Party MR Company(ies) for analytical or research purposes; and 
  4. Other uses as set forth in their privacy policy.

If you are eligible for a client survey opportunity offered through a Third-Party MR Company, the Third-Party MR Company will provide your unique identification number and a survey link to us and we will invite you to participate in the client survey through email or website. We will not share your name, or phone number with the Third-Party MR Companies. In connection with the sharing of your information with a Third-Party MR Company, your information may be transferred and stored outside of your country of residence, including, without limitation, in the United States, and by agreeing to this privacy policy you are agreeing to the processing and exportation of your personal information as set forth in this Section. If you have any questions about this data sharing, please [contact us](http://www.clixsense.com/en/Help-Submit_a_Ticket) or you can opt-out by [closing your account](https://www.clixsense.com/en/My_Account-Profile_and_Settings). If you opt-out, it is the responsibility of us to inform the Third-Party MR Companies. Please note that ClixSense is solely liable and responsible for managing all opt-out requests. Your participation in such survey opportunities does not entitle you to any benefits offered by, or membership with, the Third-Party MR Companies.

**Third party links**  
We include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third-party sites may have separate and independent privacy policies. We have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites beyond what is legally mandated. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

We work with a third-party partner LiveRamp to place a cookie on your browser that provides a de-identified, non-human readable version of your email address to use for matching to other data about you to improve the relevance of online advertising and personalization. Your actual email address is at no time shared with LiveRamp. To find out more and how to opt out [click here](http://liveramp.com/service-privacy-policy/).

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at any time by logging into their accounts and going to the [Profile and Settings](https://www.clixsense.com/en/My_Account-Profile_and_Settings) page.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
We may update this Policy from time to time. When we update this Policy, we will change the "Last Updated" date at the top of this Policy.

**How to Contact Us**  
If you have any questions or comments regarding our privacy practices or this Privacy Policy or if you would like to opt out of certain uses of your Personal Data, exercise your rights in relation to the Personal Data we hold about you or make a complaint about our privacy practice, please feel free to write to us at privacy@clixsense.com.
